Guide to the David P. Berenberg Files
Berenberg, David P. Files
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
David P. Berenberg Files, 1912-1941
5732
Berenberg, David P.
10.7 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
These files include various publications, correspondence, bills, plays, poems, collected works and collected verse.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Berenberg, David P. (David Paul), 1890-1974
Subjects:
Radicalism -- United States.
Form and Genre Terms:
Records (documents)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Related Collections:
6034: Rare Pamphlet Collection
CONTAINER LIST
- Golden Book Magazine, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Poet Lore Journal, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- The American Socialist Quarterly, 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- The World Tomorrow, The Nation Magazines, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- The Measure Poetry Journal, The Reflex, American Mercury, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Voices, Blue Peter, Menorah Journal, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Broom Magazine, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- School D.P.B, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Dr. David P. Berenberg, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Sabath Family (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Evaluation - Valley Stream (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Parnassus College Art Association (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Miriam Benton (Box 3, Folder 1)
- 1974 Doctors Bills and Medicare Forms (Box 3, Folder 2)
- American Socialist Quarterly, 1932-1935 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Collected Verse A (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1931-1933 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Bills (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 5)
- School Papers - Rose, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Socialist Party (Box 4, Folder 7)
- A.S.Q. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- P. Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Julia Talbott - a novel by David P. Berenberg Chapters 1-13 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Julia Talbott - a novel by David P. Berenberg Chapters 14-24 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Correspondences (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Franklin School (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Plays (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Writings (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Collected Works (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Collected Verse (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Miriam Benton (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Collected Verse (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Collected Verse (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Collected Verse (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Collected Verse (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Collected Verse (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Collected Verse (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Collected Verse (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Collected Verse (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Collected Verse (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Collected Verse (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Collected Verse (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Collected Verse (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Collected Verse (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Collected Verse (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Poems (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Sonnets (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Collected Verse (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Menorah Journal, 1937-1941 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- A Worker's World (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Revolution in Utopia (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Collected Verse (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Collected Verse (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Collected Verse (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Collected Verse (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Collected Verse (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Collected Verse and The Lane (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Kaiser vs. Kaiser (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Collected Verse (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Hadassah (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Collected Verse (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Collected Verse and Jewtown (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Letters (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Kantonsvitch (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Kahlstrom Fund (Box 8, Folder 16)
- The Kid by David P. Berenberg (Box 8, Folder 17)
- David P. Berenberg Tax Records Et. Al., 1927 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Letters from Magazines, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Letters from Magazines (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Socialist Journals, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Sidewalks - A Poem by David P. Berenberg (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Sonnets by David P. Berenberg (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Sidewalks - A Poem by David P. Berenberg (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Tailing (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Sarai to Glaucon (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Sidewalks, a poem by David P. Berenberg (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Copper B by Arthur Rundt (Box 10, Folder 7)
- The Milldam Road, a novel by David P. Berenberg (Box 10, Folder 8)
- The Milldam Road 2 - a novel by David P. Berenberg (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Poems (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Poems (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Poems (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Poems (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Poems (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Sonnets - Miscellany (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Poems (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Poems (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Poems (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Sarai to Glaucon (Box 10, Folder 19)
- (Box 11, Folder 6)
- State of New York: In Assembly Jan. 31, 1918 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Ledger (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous note - (Box 11, Folder 3)
  (pulled from a memo book, only page with writing)
- David P. Berenberg Scrapbook, 1919-1936 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- David Berenberg, Newspaper Clippings (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Scrapbook -- (mostly news clippings) (Box 11a, Folder 2)
- Rand School News -- v.II, no.4 -- June, 1919 (Box 11a, Folder 1)